http://www.missionstudio.com/pages/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the mission-studio.myshopify.com and Mission Studio and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Mission Studio include mission-studio.myshopify.com and Mission Studio. The Mission Studio website is a ecommerce site. By using the Mission Studio website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
Mission Studio may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. If you purchase Mission Studio's products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.
Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Mission Studio. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Mission Studio website.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Mission Studio's public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.
Mission Studio encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Mission Studio so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. We are is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Mission Studio website.
Use of your Personal Information
Mission Studio collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.
We may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Mission Studio. Mission Studio may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
Mission Studio does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.
Mission Studio may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Mission Studio, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
We may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Mission Studio, in order to determine what services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Mission Studio to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
Mission Studio will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Mission Studio or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Mission Studio; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Mission Studio, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The Mission Studio website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Mission Studio pages, or register with Mission Studio site or services, a cookie helps us recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Mission Studio website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Mission Studio features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Mission Studio services or websites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
Verisign
When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.
Verisign is an independent, third-party company engaged in the development of digital trust. Verisign provides authentication of Internet services, digital identity and intellectual property. By clicking on the Verisign logo, the Verisign website will serve up a web page that confirms that Mission Studio is "Verisign Authenticated."
Children Under Thirteen
Mission Studio does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.
Changes to this Statement
Mission Studio will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. We encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Mission Studio is protecting your information.
